Subtitles edited by DiskKun
Showbox / Mediaplex presents
a Showbox / Mediaplex
and MaysEntertainment production
in association with AzitFilm
LOSING MOVE:
THE MOVE RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR DEFEAT
You have 30 seconds left.
30, 29, 28, 27, 26, 25...
Put up an umbrella.
Is that you?
I saw your game.
One poor move ruined it.
I'm sorry.
Fight like a man.
Never back off.
Where have you been?
We can chat later.
Right now I've got a favor to ask you.
Play a guidance game for me.
Guidance game?
With who?
It doesn't matter who.
Please, it won't take long.
Do we have to do this?
I have a bad feeling about it.
Don't worry. We'll win.
What kind of game is this?
Just play as you always have.
It'll be easy.
Are you gambling?
It's none of your business.
Tae-seok!
Tae-seok! Tae-seok!
Wait! Tae-seok!
Listen to me.
You have to do this for me.
You cannot lose.
Understand?
You have to win.
Just trust me.
I'll be fine.
On 5 and 12.
Your skill's improved drastically.
It's just luck.
You're sweating.
Why don't you take your jacket off?
True dandies can sweat to death
for the sake of fashion.
Is that so? I've only got swagger
in the winter.
Wow, he is a tough match!
He plays sharp.
A real pro.
Take over.
Boss, I can handle this.
Sit.
On 12 and 12.
Stretch.
On 6 and 6.
I can't hold it.
I'll be right back.
You go on.
Brother.
Can you hear me?
On 9 and 12.
Attack.
On 13 and 8. Escape with a
Large Knight's move.
On 7 and 4.
- How's it going?
- It's strange.
- Why?
- He suddenly got much stronger.
How come Black is
suddenly moving so fast?
Holy cow!
What is wrong with me?
I'm sorry. I need to
go to the toilet again.
I can't see the board right now.
Wait a bit.
Don't make a move.
You're slower than usual today.
Can you hear me?
Just linger over.
No, that's the wrong spot!
Don't put it there.
Please don't!
Finish it.
Brother, something's wrong.
Come out right now!
You hear me?
Get out of there!
Tae-seok!
I'm sorry.
You little prick.
Having a shadow player
at a gentlemen's game?
Learn some fucking manners!
Even the money is fake.
You know what the
consequences are for that?
Please, don't!
Quiet.
I'm sorry, sir!
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive us.
- Shut the fuck up!
- Brother!
Brother!
Wait! We're not done yet.
Eat the stones.
Or your brother is dead.
If you win,
I'll let your brother go.
Start.
No takesies-backsies.
It just dropped!
That's nonsense...
Please let me take it back.
Just one move.
Please...
Don't kill my brother.
I'm sorry.
Please don't kill him.
My brother...
I... I'm done!
There's one left!
Go and life are quite similar.
One bad move...
leads you to death.
Brother!
Look at the true dandy stabbed to death!
Dead stones are
removed from the board.
JUNG Woo-sung
LEE Bum-soo
AHN Sung-ki
KIM In-Kwon
LEE Si-young
AN Kil-kang
CHOI Jin-hyuk
THE DIVINE MOVE
Mr. Director, I'd like to have
a couple of days' leave-time.
Leave-time?
I need to check the regulation.
Should be quite tight on things like that.
You know, the Japanese police
once investigated
a sample of 500 criminals
and found one common point.
Can you guess what it was?
Not a single one played Go.
What does it mean?
That the criminals who play Go
seldom get caught.
The ones playing Go
Why?
They can see the moves ahead.
In that sense, I can say
you're one of two cases.
Either you cannot play Go,
or are very dumb.
A week will do.
Win a game against me,
then I'll let you go out.
A large group got captured.
Is this where he got me?
It seems so.
It's like I'll die
stuck in this prison.
Not quite.
Let him come near.
A large group of stones
is seldom captured.
Play a game with a man here.
He's quite good.
No one's ever beaten him.
You damn fucker.
I like you!
Playing with the dumpsters
was getting boring.
One more game!
And don't forget to make a bet.
He's addicted to it.
Please do me a favor if I win.
Tell me.
I want beer, cigarettes and
free time till I serve my sentence.
You wanna play for stakes?
Only if you'll allow me.
Then what's your bet?
You won.
Request for leave-days
GRANTED
But you get one month
in the solitary cell for being so cocky.
A game, please?
On 7 and 3.
On 5 and 12.
On 12 and 9...
Who are you?
Let me at least know your name.
Your company obliterated
my loneliness. Thanks.
Look for a man named Drinking Christ
at Gwancheol when you get out.
Thanks for your trouble.
Now that I have some free time...
Please train me how to fight.
Wow! Unbelievable.
Help yourself!
I got first prize!
Wanna work for me
when you get out?
I've got work to do.
Please do me one favor.
I need some money.
I'll pay you back.
It's me who owed you.
I'll buy you drinks, then.
As long as you are alive
till I get out.
Was a tough search.
She's a real treasure.
He had a hard time finding her.
Two.
He asks for two million.
You've got 10 minutes. Test her.
Ah, it's not enough time.
These are tsumego. You know them?
Ten minutes to solve them.
Understand?
Black to play.
I'm changing the amount.
Three million.
Fuck off if you can't pay it.
Now he wants three million.
Wait!
Fine. Call me when you have
good stuff of your own.
Go kill them.
But bring the girl alive.
Bring Navel in.
Can we play?
This is not a ladies' game.
How many handicap stones
do you want?
No handicap.
All in.
Master Noh, you'd better focus on training
the young now that you retired.
Who the hell are you?
You don't belong here.
You're still okay, I guess.
Don't eat too much.
I don't like chubby girls.
Do you give boss a special service?
He treats you too well.
We can play a game with your
life as bet, if you dare.
You can get two
handicap stones.
Intimidated?
Maybe I'll put a
"special service" as a bet.
Oh, I forgot you can't come.
Stick to what you are.
Using those dumb brains
of yours will make you sick.
Don't you agree?
Thanks for the advice.
Damn, I surely can come.
Good job.
Take that kid.
Wash and feed her.
I'm not really into parenting.
I'm hungry.
How old are you?
Seven?
Eight?
You're ten years old.
Your name?
Liang Liang?
PLACEMENT: PLACE YOUR STONE
ON THE BOARD
Is your mom coming?
Why?
Dead.
Do you play Go?
No, Five in a Row.
Grandma said she'll kill me if I play Go.
Are you really my uncle?
See you soon.
My reading ability
is off today.
I was just lucky.
Sir, can I play a game
with the gentleman over there?
Mr. Cho, he wants
to play a game with you.
You have similar ranks.
I lost this time too.
One more game?
Aren't you broke?
I think I got $500 left.
Why don't you save it
for a rainy day?
Then how about we play for
flicks on the forehead?
Wait a bit.
Just one more hour.
Have you collected?
Of course! A bountiful harvest.
I'm playing with a pushover
I ripped $10,000 off of him already.
This broke blockhead
lost his temper
and wants to put bashes
with the knuckles as a bet!
Sir.
Why don't you go out
and drink while we play?
Alright! Well...
Shall we count?
Let's see.
I won by half a point.
I can see you're good at counting.
Then...
Let me see.
You can keep the change
as the winner's tip!
We had another bet.
What?
Ten blows with the knuckles.
You're tilting because you lost a lot today?
You're quite persistent.
Got it.
Give me a blow!
Then...
Learn some fucking manners!
Hit me.
Are you fucking crazy?
You fucker, where should I
put your dead body?
The left corner or right?
Tengen? Hoshi?
Son of a bitch!
Untie me right now!
Do you hear me? Hey!
What the hell!
Who are you?
I guess you didn't
review the game.
What?
What are you talking about?
You little prick.
You surely grew up.
So what do you want me to do?
What shall I do for you?
What are you doing?
Oh, I see.
Hit me! I'm not afraid!
Two more blows to go.
Son of a bitch.
You can go to hell.
I'm wondering if your brother
has finished digesting...
All the stones in his stomach.
The game starts now.
Play with your hand, not your tongue.
Atari!
Can you just shut up and play?
Damn, I should've noticed that trick.
What trick?
My life's all about fair play.
There's so many black stones.
It's like a coal mine.
Hello? Wait there.
It won't take long,
I'm just inside the building.
You lied about
your rank, didn't you?
If I were any better,
I'd take the pro exam.
I never lie about two things.
My Go rank and my endurance.
Thanks for the game!
Catch that prick!
Help me! Help!
Don't kill me. I'm only 6!
You tried to cheat us?
It was a fair game...
Wanna cough up the money
or the blood in your body?
The money, of course!
Can I speak to him for a minute?
What? Is he with you?
You know Woo-seok?
No.
Mr. Song Woo-seok.
Who are you?
I know! I know, I know him!
I remember you!
You're his younger brother!
So you're alive?
Wow I'm thrilled.
My first time teaming up with a pro.
Wow, look at this place.
It's like a movie set.
How did you meet my brother?
You really don't know?
We were on the same team.
Trying to survive.
Your brother was a well known devil.
I mean, a professional gambler.
Poor Woo-seok.
He shouldn't have died like that.
Have you seen this guy?
You know, I pulled out of
the league a long time ago.
You go on your own.
I'm out of this.
Join me if you change your mind.
You'll get the half of the profit.
3 million.
I am back not because of the money!
But because I want to repay
your brother's kindness!
I got you, right? I'm good at acting,
I know. Am I in?
Hey, Master Song.
What kind of Go master
plays at a place like this?
No way! Not a chance.
Listen. The two of us can split it.
We don't need more players.
It gets too complicated.
You're stubborn as a mule.
Wait, Master Song!
Is this group dead?
Guess I had a better luck.
How did I let the large group die?
Damn!
Don't tell me it's THE master.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you please have
a conversation with me?
I'm not very good with conversations
but I surely can talk with drinks.
The bet is a bottle of drink, then.
Please teach me a lesson, sir.
I lost by half a point.
You're much stronger than me.
Why are you sounding me out?
Let's have a drink.
Okay. Let's get "baptized
by the sacred water".
Now I know why people
call you Drinking Christ.
It's so good.
Have we met before?
Definitely not.
What happened to your eyes?
It was an accident.
I also lost my eye
in an accident.
I've got a plan.
Just take care of the other eye.
We can win.
That blind belief
drives people to death.
Will you join us?
Thank you for the drink.
Do the blind dream?
Sure, mostly nightmares.
And when you're awake?
The nightmares continue.
Is that your daughter?
How does she look?
Good and sound.
Why don't you decide?
What's your name?
You can call me Big Move.
And you can call me Agnus Dei!
Let's go.
Are you here, Carpenter?
I think you're lost.
It's been a while.
Can we talk for a minute?
You're still drunk.
Go on your way.
Can I have water?
Here you are.
Why? You thought I lost
both of my hands?
I'm sorry.
We were quite okay once.
The happy ending isn't
for the gamblers.
What brings you here?
I'm fighting against them again.
Then this is the last time
that I see you alive.
Help us.
OPENING: PREPARE FOR THE FIGHT
I've been to the gambling parlor
run by Killer.
It's perfectly organized.
He's Player.
He's good Go, but
better at acting.
He's more like the manager
of the house.
Gamblers around the nation
come here to play.
They can't cheat each other...
as everyone is better than average.
Some games have a huge bet.
That's the VIP room,
they take 10% of the bet.
Player finds some rich guys
to play with him.
Mainly the rich businessmen
or ones in high-class jobs,
who have a lot of pride
and are very competitive.
We got a real pushover!
Once he traps you, it takes
less than a month to go broke.
That snake-like old man is their
guidance player.
He's Master Wang.
He runs a calligraphy academy
but it's just a front.
The monthly tuition is $500 for
children and $700 for adults
and the minimum term length is
3 months. So greedy.
Great skill, though.
That ugly son of a bitch
in the flower shirt is Atari.
He's the collector, and runs the
illegal online gambling, too.
The meanest of all
is this one, Killer.
Damn violent son of a bitch.
Hey Big Move!
Can we leave him alone?
Who's that girl?
Damn. Attention everyone!
Open your eyes, Drinking Christ.
Have you heard of the Goddess Bar?
25-year-old Kwon runs it.
She turned pro at 15.
Gold medalist at the Doha Asian Games.
World Champion in 2006.
But she retired and disappeared
when she turned just 20.
And ta-da, now she runs this bar.
They call her Navel.
Navel is another term
for a star point on the goban.
I think she belongs to Killer.
I need to leave after this game.
Let's play one more.
Just as the game starts to go well!
Sorry sir.
My wife is pregnant.
What? Bad play!
Well, I won this time too.
$600 each, please.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- It's your lucky day.
- I guess so.
Hey, young man! Are you here to play?
Come and join us!
What do you do for a living?
I'm a researcher in school.
Research?
You mean a professor? What major?
Math.
Math! Which university?
I have a friend
at Seoul National University.
He had a stroke
while playing mah-jong with me.
But when I said we were
one short to play,
he suddenly woke up
and played again!
Anyway, great to meet you.
You know what the most difficult
thing to do in mah-jong is?
Nine Gates? Hell no.
Gathering four to play a game.
Such a hassle.
How did you find this place?
I've been here once,
a long time ago.
I don't recall your face. I'm quite good
at remembering faces.
I was very different back then.
You play Go, too?
More as a hobby.
I also play it a bit.
Let's play together someday.
Have we met before?
Well...
Thanks for the talk.
I can't do it!
What is Carpenter doing?
Making a chair?
Give it to me.
Wow, you can make
this kinda stuff, too!
You look a bit awkward.
What can you see?
Driver's License
YOOK Jong-duck
6 Ducks Entertainment!
Feels... sexy.
Lost again!
This seat is unlucky!
This seat too! And this, too!
I'm getting ripped off!
Where is the lucky seat?
Hey, the cigarettes!
- One more game!
- No problem!
You don't have 1 millimeter?
You wanna suffocate me
with nicotine?
One more game!
You have it all!
- One more game. Wait here. Don't move!
- I won't.
Wait right there!
I need some money.
You don't look like
the brainy type.
You can tell?
Then you're in the wrong job.
My brain cells are all dead!
- What does he do?
- He makes adult films.
How much did he spend?
Hundred thousand.
Low skill, but high in pride.
A perfect target.
HAENGMA: SHAPE OF THE STONES
Carpenter, did test this out?
You didn't do a lousy job, did you?
I need a bonus
for risking my life.
The smoking will kill me
even if I don't get stabbed.
Stop drinking!
How can you play?
Kyu player worries much.
What if I'm a
master in disguise?
I sometimes think so, seeing you
treat the world
as a playground.
The world is a playground
for the dans...
and a living hell
for the kyus.
That makes me
the lowest of the low.
For me, the world
is an endless hell.
Go for a fast attack. Divide
wedge through the center of the left.
Approaching on 3 and 6.
Lower Pincer by one space.
On 12 and 12.
On 16 and 9.
On 10 and 9.
Good job.
Hey!
Search this bastard.
What are you talking about?
You lost one game, so you lose your
temper too? I've lost enough here!
Let go of me, shitheads!
Nothing? Wow! I'm clear. Poor you!
Losing is painful!
You see now?
You petty bastard!
I will kill you, son of a bitch!
You're dead!
What the hell are you doing?
Mind your own boards!
Mind your own games, I said!
Sir.
- Would you have a game with me?
- I'm not in the mood.
Don't let a petty bastard
ruin your mood.
What's your rank?
What matters is not the rank,
but the condition of the day.
Right, just like sex!
Let me get some fresh air first.
Sure.
I hate cigarettes.
Have I told you
how much I'm amazed
by your marvelous survival skills?
Speak for yourself.
There aren't many options
for low-lifes like us.
I'm not like you.
I'm playing on the center stage.
We're in different leagues, dude.
Center or corner, the last man
standing takes the pot.
A hell of disguise...
Fuck off!
Such a rat.
Here we are again.
We're meant to
live like this, I guess.
Have you ever seen a divine move?
No, I haven't.
Is there such a move, in life?
A move so powerful that it can change
our life so dramatically.
Only God knows.
What would you do with
such a move?
I would save your arm.
And my wife.
I can think of a better move.
Go back to when you
didn't play for money.
I won.
Congratulations.
It's your lucky day.
I'm done here.
Again today?
My luck's finally here!
It's my wedding anniversary.
Damn the anniversaries.
Mister! Come join us.
How can you make a living
if you quit teaching?
I'm building a program.
A program? What kind?
A kind of algorithm for Go.
Alg... what?
A computer program
that can beat humans
at Go.
What's the point for computers
to be good at Go?
Like it's not hard enough for us.
I won.
What the shit?
Nine Gates?
It's once-in-a-lifetime luck!
Congratulations, really.
Thank you.
Let me buy you dinner.
Of course, you should!
I have to go, sorry.
You shouldn't go home today.
It'd bring you bad luck.
You should play all night.
Where should we go?
I know a good lamb place.
You'd better go home.
I won first.
But I passed for you.
- I didn't know that.
- You better watch out.
You had once-in-a-lifetime luck today.
You might die soon.
I'm dead already.
I've got no more life to lose.
Caller ID: Killer
Hello.
What is he?
He really is a programmer.
His hands look too rough
for a computer guy.
Maybe he smashes keyboards
when he's pissed off.
You feel like joking?
I guess the date was fun.
Partners shouldn't have secrets.
No partnership is eternal.
And your bad fortune this year
could affect the business.
I saved your mother.
Are you forgetting the terms?
It's a lifetime deal.
It terminates when you die.
You never know.
Your death could also terminate it.
Your endgame is riddled
with bad moves.
Don't try so hard.
You're a ladder.
You'll end up dead
no matter how long you chase it for.
Look for the ladder breaker
before you kill. You could miss it.
A common mistake for kyus.
It's not easy...
Hopeless bastard.
How did it go?
What keeps you so busy?
Share some of the fun stuff with us!
How was it today?
Christ had a hell of a good move.
Masters never hesitate.
Go by yourself tomorrow.
You want me to walk into
the lion's den alone?
Don't worry.
He'll let you win.
What does that mean?
Hey, tell me!
Today's not the day for me.
Thanks for a good game.
- It's for your fare.
- That's alright.
You act so cool.
How about betting bigger next time?
Why not?
You're dead meat!
DANSOO [ATARI]: ONE MOVE AWAY
FROM BEING CAPTURED.
It's what I do.
Our target market is China.
It's the second biggest
movie market.
Care for a sneak peek?
Let's start the game.
- Right away?
- Sure.
I gotta take a leak first.
Try this in your mouth.
It feels good!
This business is in recession, too.
People watch porn on their phones
nowadays. So it doesn't earn any money.
Movies gotta have soul in it.
But it's all about moaning now.
What will the youngsters
learn from it?
I can't help but worry
about this country's future.
Are you OK with this location?
I feel bad that I chose
my home grounds.
- Let's keep it quiet.
- This is how I loosen up.
- How about having a smoke?
- I quit.
The human lung is such a delicate organ,
that can be compared to a lotus...
Keep your mouth shut, I said.
Oh my God, what's this?
I thought I lost but
I won by one and a half points?
I will keep this in custody.
It's heavy.
Show some respect, dude.
How much did you lose?
Two large bills.
How large?
2 million?
Since when did you become
such a pushover?
Don't get on my nerves.
There's a saying, "man is most
prideful just before he falls."
Never let down your guard
at this level of play!
Shut up and help me tomorrow.
By the way...
Does Killer know about this?
Don't wag your tongue.
What's the split?
60, 40 as always.
Let's do 50, 50.
Are you trying to negotiate with me?
Well, I'm not the one who's
got his back to the edge.
Greedy men never
age gracefully.
If you look at me like that again,
I'll kill you myself.
- You don't have to count?
- No need.
It feels better to count at home.
You won't have to do
any counting today.
It's Dansoo, Atari!
I can see.
Shut your mouth.
Who's this bastard?
He's not taking the bait!
On 5 and 9.
Don't blow smoke in my face.
Tons of trick moves...
I recognize this playstyle.
Long time no see, you kibitzer.
Take the bait,
you son of a bitch!
Bastards!
Didn't you quit?
I quit quitting.
I got dumped by a chick.
I'm getting curious
how big your mouth can get.
This son of a bitch!
Now he's playing me?
Player, on 6 and 4.
He's pushing forward.
Women are scary creatures.
We were together for so long
but she cut me off just like that.
Quite similar to Go.
When they cut you off,
This motherfucker
is totally playing me!
They do so mercilessly.
They're messing with us!
Screw the game!
You hear me? Screw it!
What the hell!
Please don't kill me!
I beg you.
I better get a big bonus for this!
I don't remember inviting you.
Use the dagger, if you want.
Came for a brain game
but forced to use brawn.
Brawn is a part of Go, too.
Beat him to death!
I'll have to let you
play alone, Player.
What the hell!
Hold on tight!
SPIN AROUND ATTACK:
ATTACKING BY SERIES OF FATAL MOVES
The rules are simple.
The winner gets out.
What's all this about?
Let's play a quick game
before we freeze.
You should play a move before
the sand runs out. Your move.
Come on!
Look at the winter swagger
frozen to death.
Look at the true dandy
stabbed to death!
This is a tsumego.
One move to make the group live.
That's the padlock code.
I need a drink.
A warm one.
You look terrible.
How about a game?
For fun or for a bet?
Well, you'll get more fun
by betting something.
What should the bet be?
Granting a wish?
Too childish.
Childish, but of tradition.
This is a unique board.
Are they goddesses?
Goddess of fortune and
goddess of destruction.
- Which one am I?
- Destruction suits you.
The width of the board is 45 centimeters.
The perfect distance
for sharing feelings.
How can people
share their feelings?
It would be like
making you mine.
Dansoo.
I won't be easy.
Good move.
I was just lucky.
Be careful what you wish for.
You're definitely
getting my attention.
How about a game?
It'd be exciting
to put our lives on the line.
I like it.
Can't wait to see you.
I left you a gift
at the calligraphy academy.
Also, turn off the freezer.
And open the cabinet.
Open the cabinet!
Untie him.
What took you so long?
Hurry!
Log on with ID: Master Wang
PW: QWER34
Boss, I saw him!
Sit here.
Let go of me, bastards.
What's going on?
I didn't do anything!
Player forced me to do it!
I didn't steal the money!
6 million is my bet. I need
his tongue as yours.
Do not listen to him.
I'll pay off the shortfall.
We're partners!
Don't be foolish!
CARPE DIEM requested a game.
Press ACCEPT or DECLINE.
Please, don't do this to me!
Accept it.
It's a trap!
I told you to accept.
Good, I will crush this bastard!
Got a cigarette?
Do you know why I like Go
of all the games?
Because it's a brain game.
Petty tricks don't work.
It's the smart ones who win.
Isn't it beautifully simple?
Give me some water, assholes!
Point counting requested.
Accept.
Congratulations!
White won by half a point.
Still reviewing the game?
Flip the goban on the table over.
Flip it over.
See the hole?
It's called the "blood flow".
It's a hole to fill with the blood
from the Master's tongue.
Please, I will get him.
I promise!
I will get him to you!
I'll get him!
Please don't do that!
Evil leaves the mouth...
By the way, the window sign
is missing a letter.
It smells fantastic!
Is it cooked yet?
Come on, Big Move!
Let's have a feast!
Do you guys know why I play Go?
Confucius once said, "It's better
to play Go than to do nothing all day."
You should listen to the sages.
Christ, how did you become a Master
without being able to see?
Give us the secret!
I looked over others' shoulders.
Seriously, come on!
I want to know the secret!
When I was selling junk
on the street,
someone came to me.
He told me he'd seen me before.
And he invited me to play Go.
I told him I couldn't play
because I'm blind.
Then he gave me a present.
Stones for the blind.
We played Go every day.
He was a true master.
A real one.
And after exactly one year,
he stopped showing up.
He might be the one who
told me about you.
Have you seen him?
No.
When I was in solitary confinement,
we used to play Go, banging
on the walls. I lost every time.
Who's there?
Tell me who you are!
But there was no chalk
in his cell.
It's simple.
He never marked anything.
You mean he played
blind Go?
He played the entire game in his head
and beat Big Move? Impossible.
I heard that there's a
player like this in Busan.
They call him the Ghost.
Ghost?
Cheater, do you have a minute?
Please do me a favor.
I won't buy drinks for you.
I quit drinking.
Next you'll tell
me you can see.
What do you want?
Christ, you're damn good looking!
You blushed.
It's too funny.
Oh my God!
Chicks will be all over you!
Don't worry so much.
Your daughter must be glad.
Well... it seems like
we need to run.
This way!
Wait.
You damn bastard.
Not today!
It's a big day for us!
Bring it on!
WEAK GROUP: ENDANGERED STONES
SURROUNDED BY THE OPPONENT
What a surprise, that we
should meet again like this.
I've prepared a fun game.
One of my men died
because he couldn't solve
this tsumego.
You will have three chances.
Can I play seated?
I think my toes are broken.
Game on.
Two chances left.
Please have mercy.
Game on again.
Last chance.
Please, I beg you.
I guess it's your lucky day.
Rest in peace, my love.
I recognize you now.
I thought I killed you.
I was dead, but now I'm born again.
I'll change your fate, too.
The bet is 6 million on top of
your buddy's head.
I can't wait to see who will win.
Try your damn best.
Your life is on it.
How about betting
my life instead of his?
Christ...
Cheer up.
We'll have a drink after this game.
But I don't have stones
for the blind here.
I will play the blind Go.
No, Christ, you shouldn't!
Blind Go?
No, you can't!
- You should help me.
- Christ, please don't!
Playing a blind game?
Why?
You can't beat a blind man?
I'll show mercy, and end
your life as fast as I can.
Star point on upper left corner.
Strong opening for an old man.
Quite provocative.
Low 3-4 point on lower left corner.
I can't fight
against an elder.
I'll dodge.
Opposite 3-4 point
on upper right corner.
Star point on lower right corner.
Starting the fight so soon?
Right 3-4 point on upper right corner.
I don't want to fight.
I'll cut your throat if I win.
Knight's approach
on upper right corner.
Don't fight back.
Large Knight on upper right corner.
As you like.
I'll go my own way.
Large Knight stretched
on lower left corner.
Lower Pincer by 3 spaces
on upper right corner.
You're scaring me. I'll run away.
Center, cover the cap.
On 10 and 10.
Dodge.
He's the one who struggles,
not us.
Diamond on the zenith.
Choke lower side by a territory.
Knight's move
on right side of center. Attack now.
on left side of center.
On 14 and 13. Cut it!
Got him!
We got him!
You're dead meat, motherfucker!
On 7 and 7.
- He just cut it.
- Move forward!
You better be ready to die.
A scumbag like you
couldn't play like that.
Nice moves...
for a blind man.
Listen, Cheater.
The world isn't a playground to me.
I'm sorry.
The drinks should wait.
Review the game in your grave.
I nailed Drinking Christ to the board.
Sorry.
If you win,
I will spare his life.
Big Move... Don't worry.
I can't make it anyways.
- I will come back.
- No, don't!
Don't play the game.
You can't win.
He can't be beaten. The moves
are too subtle.
It must be a kid playing.
An innocent one.
You better do your best
if you want a happy ending.
Keep the kid out of this.
- Kill them both if I lose.
- Yes, sir.
How many handicaps would you take
if you played against the god of Go?
Two.
- If your life's on it?
- Three.
If there is a god of Go,
it must be a child, right?
Stop here.
- Are you scared of me?
- You'll never win.
LIFE AND DEATH:
ONE MOVE TO STAY ALIVE
Kill the Carpenter.
Same opening as the blind man.
3-3 point? Not very much
influence, playing in the corner.
Cover on the star point.
Double 3-3 point?
You're too defensive.
Can we start the fight already?
Come with us.
Let me see if there's
a way out for me, first.
Life and death
is always difficult.
That's why it starts the fight.
Let's see who lives
and who dies.
You'll regret it.
I'll make it painful.
Are you throwing a stone,
or making a move?
It's a move.
Did you know that she dies if you win?
Don't even think about it.
What're you waiting for?
On 8 and 10, cap on center.
Attack.
He made the losing move.
On 1 and 2, move forward.
On 3 and 3, connect.
On 4 and 1.
Bend.
It's Eternal Life.
We're even.
We can play forever
or you can yield.
What if I don't want to yield?
Then we're even.
Being even isn't part of my plan.
Then we should
finish this here.
Interesting.
It doesn't get better than this.
Bring the bitch.
How do we end this?
Have you seen all the stones
on the board disappear?
Take a close look.
You'll witness that.
Wearing protection?
How manly...
SCORING: END THE GAME
AND CALL THE VICTOR
I worked for your father.
He left something for you.
How have you been?
Keep this.
And call me three times a day.
Isn't it too cold out?
My hands are warm as ever.
Christ once asked me
if there's a divine move in life.
I now understand
there's no such move.
The best move we can make
is to live every day.
Where are we heading now?
To Busan.
THE DIVINE MOVE
Life and Death
Directed by JO Bum-go